Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2018
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Brad Lubman, conductor speaks with Greg Chudzik, double bass and xxx speaks with composer David Felder after rehearsal of David Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9935.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_165.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor speaks with composer David Felder after a rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9938.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_166.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer rehearse Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00584.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_167.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer rehearse Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00585.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_168.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaks with Signal Ensemble member Greg Chudzik, double bass as Brad Lubman, conductor and other Signal Ensemble members and guests Irvine Arditti, violin and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello look on after a rehearsal of Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9940.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_169.tif)
- Aaron Holloway-Nahum, sound engineer adjusts a microphone above Irvine Arditti, violin during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9942.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_170.tif)
- Aaron Holloway-Nahum, sound engineer adjusts a microphone above Irvine Arditti, violin during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9943.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_171.tif)
- Close up of a double bass microphone with Signal Ensemble members Olivia De Prato, violin, Kelli Kathman, flute, and Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola in the background during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9945.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_172.tif)
- Paul Hembree, computer rehearsing Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9946.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_173.tif)
- Paul Hembree, computer rehearsing Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9951.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_174.tif)
- Paul Hembree, computer rehearsing Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9954.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_175.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds speaks with Paul Hembree, computer during rehearsal of Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9957Roger Reynolds.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_176.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds speaks with Paul Hembree, computer during rehearsal of Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9958.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_177.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds speaks with Paul Hembree, computer during rehearsal of Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9959.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_178.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds speaks with Paul Hembree, computer during rehearsal of Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9963.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_179.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer rehearse Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9965.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_180.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer rehearse Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9966.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_181.tif)
- Composer Hilda Paredes at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9971 copy.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_182.tif)
- Composer Hilda Paredes at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9971.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_183.tif)
- Composer John Harbison giving a seminar to student composers at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9972.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_184.tif)
- Composer John Harbison giving a seminar to student composers at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9974.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_185.tif)
- Composer John Harbison giving a seminar to student composers at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9975John Harbison.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_186.tif)
- Composer John Harbison giving a seminar to student composers at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9976.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_187.tif)
- Composer John Harbison giving a seminar to student composers at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9977.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_188.tif)
- Composer John Harbison giving a seminar to student composers at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9978.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_189.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Olivia De Prato and Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, and Mariel Roberts, violoncello in rehearsal of Mathew Arrellin's Cacodemonic at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9979.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_190.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin performing Hilda Paredes' piece In Memoriam Thomas Kakuska at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00587.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_191.tif)
- Composers Roger Reynolds, Hilda Paredes, and Hans Thomalla posing at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9981.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_192.tif)
- Composers Roger Reynolds, Hilda Paredes, and Hans Thomalla posing at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9985.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_193.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer perform Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9988.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_194.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer perform Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9992.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_195.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer perform Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9994.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_196.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer perform Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9995.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_197.tif)
- Composer Hans Thomalla coaches Irvine Arditti violin, on Thomalla's piece Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9998.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_198.tif)
- Composer Hans Thomalla coaches Irvine Arditti violin, on Thomalla's piece Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9999.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_199.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin performs Hans Thomalla's piece Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0002.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_200.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin performs Hans Thomalla's piece Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0005.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_201.tif)
- Composer Hilda Paredes acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin after a performance of Paredes' piece In Memoriam Thomas Kakuska at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0011Hilda Paredes.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_202.tif)
- Composer Hilda Paredes acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin after a performance of Paredes' piece In Memoriam Thomas Kakuska at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0012Hilda Paredes.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_203.tif)
- Composer Hilda Paredes acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin after a performance of Paredes' piece In Memoriam Thomas Kakuska at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0013.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_204.tif)
- Composer Hans Thomalla acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin after a performance of Thomalla's piece Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0015.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_205.tif)
- Composer Hans Thomalla acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin after a performance of Thomalla's piece Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0016.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_206.tif)
- Composer Hans Thomalla acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin after a performance of Thomalla's piece Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0017.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_207.tif)
- Composer Hans Thomalla acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin after a performance of Thomalla's piece Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0018Hans Thomalla.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_208.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer acknowledge applause after a performance of Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0019Paul Hembree.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_209.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer after a performance of Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0024.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_210.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer after a performance of Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0025.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_211.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer after a performance of Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0028.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_212.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds acknowledges Irvine Arditti, violin and Paul Hembree, computer after a performance of Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0031.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_213.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Hannah Levinson, viola, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Ito, clarinet, and Kelley Barnett, flute in rehearsal of Hans Thomalla's piece Momentsmusicaux at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00595.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_214.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Seuhiro, piano, Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, and Yumi Ito, bass clarinet in rehearsal of Roger Reynolds' piece Shadowed Narrative at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00605.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_215.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds coaches Moon Young Ha, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En members Maria Im, violin and Yumi Ito, bass clarinet at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00606Roger Reynolds.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_216.tif)
- Composer Hans Thomalla and Moon Young Ha, conductor pose at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0045.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_217.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Suehiro, piano, Mark Broschinsky, trombone, Yumi Ito, clarinet, Kelley Barnett, flute, and Josh Perry, percussion in a performance of Louis Karchin's piece As the Circle Opens to Infinity... at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00610.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_218.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Suehiro, piano, Kelley Barnett, flute, Mark Broschinsky, trombone, Yumi Ito, clarinet, and Josh Perry, percussion in a performance of Louis Karchin's piece As the Circle Opens to Infinity... at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00615.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_219.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, and Yumi Ito, clarinet in a performance of Roger Reynolds' piece Shadowed Narrative at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00627.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_220.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds acknowledges Moon Young Ha, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Maria Im, violin, and Maria Hadge, violoncello after a performance of Reynolds' piece Shadowed Narrative at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00630 Roger Reynolds.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_221.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Hannah Levinson, viola, Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Ito, clarinet, and Kelley Barnett, flute in a performance of Hilda Paredes' piece Siphonophorae at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00631 Hilda Paredes.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_222.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Hannah Levinson, viola, Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Ito, clarinet, and Kelley Barnett, flute in a performance of Hilda Paredes' piece Siphonophorae at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00631.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_223.tif)
- Composer Hilda Paredes acknowledges Moon Young Ha, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Hannah Levinson, viola, Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Ito, clarinet, and Kelley Barnett, flute after a performance of Paredes' piece Siphonophorae at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00632.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_224.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Maria Im, violin, Mark Broschinsky, trombone, Yumi Ito, clarinet, Josh Perry, percussion, and Kelley Barnett in a performance of Louis Karchin's piece As the Circle Opens to Infinity... at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00633.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_225.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin acknowledges Moon Young Ha, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En members Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Mark Broschinsky, trombone, Yumi Ito, clarinet, Josh Perry, percussion, and Kelley Barnett, flute after a performance of Karchin's piece As the Circle Opens to Infinity... at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00634.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_226.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En members Maria Im, violin, Hannah Levinson, viola, Yumi Ito, clarinet, Kelley Barnett, flute, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Suehiro, piano, Josh Perry, percussion, and Mark Broschinsky, trombone pose with composers Louis Karchin, Roger Reynolds, and Hans Thomalla after a performance of their works at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00637.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_227.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En members Maria Im, violin, Hannah Levinson, viola, Yumi Ito, clarinet, Kelley Barnett, flute, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Suehiro, piano, Josh Perry, percussion, and Mark Broschinsky, trombone pose with composers Louis Karchin, Roger Reynolds, and Hans Thomalla after a performance of their works at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00638.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_228.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En members Maria Im, violin, Hannah Levinson, viola, Yumi Ito, clarinet, Kelley Barnett, flute, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Suehiro, piano, Josh Perry, percussion, and Mark Broschinsky, trombone pose with composers Louis Karchin and Roger Reynolds after a performance of their works at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0062.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_229.tif)